(Concept by)
(Screenplay)
(Directed by)
Mom!
Yes
I've just arrived safe and sound
you can stop worrying
Nope!
the ship didn't sink this time either
...do you think you're talking to my ghost?
No! I'm not coming home mom, told you!
Yes, yes
I'm wondering how I'm going to survive, too
with those two airheads as roommates
but you gotta give up
Yes, yes, Debora is coming
...about which..
yep, speak of the devil...
No, look, Gaia, at best
would have come on a bike, you know
C'mon! Gotta hang up. I promise I'll call you back once I'm at the flat
All good? Ok?
C'mon, yep, you're gonna tell me all about auntie, later!
All good, come on! Ok!
Gotta hang  up, come on, bye kiss, byebyebye! Hanging up now? Bye!
Matey!
MATEY!
Hold on!
(deb_mele At the seaport to pick up my bestie and #bff #besties #love #friends #smile #fun #aardvark)
Dearie! How have I missed you!
Hm... Me too!
What are you doing out there?
C'mon, get in!
Ehm, no, really...  I should put my suitcase in the boot first
Ehmm... I believe they can't all fit in.
Let's do this: you hold the shoe case on your lap.
No, I didn't make myself clear
SUIT-CASE
Noun. One. Singular.
Yes, only one, eh! An adventurer as usual!
Then it's going to fit, for sure.
How was the trip, Bestie?
Look, the usual
You have such dark circles..
An hour late
The air conditioner in the cabin was out of order
and the inevitable sea sickness during the whole trip
But... is it even possible that you haven't seen my make-up tutorial on how to fix dark circles, yet?
Bestie, you offend me, it's one of the earliest I made!
Look, I'll explain that to you in person, just because it's you
First of all you'll need a (primer) to
enhance the (corrector's) effect
Bestie, the latter must be coloured in peach, categorically!
because, dearie, your complexion asks for it!
If one had to use an orange shade
for the blue of the dark circles
(Pollo: Pollo to Pingu: you still alive? Shall I come over and pick you up from the Islands of Oceania?)
what would obviously happen?
You'd resemble Gollum in no time
(Pingu: Return to homeland achieved, my naughty chick)
This is obviously only the beginning
(Pollo: Damn, I have bought a machete for nothing. Are you at home already?)
and then you'll need some foundation
of the same colour of your skin. Trust me,
Bestie, be careful! We both know you are wrong
(Pingu: On my way. If you feel like, meet me at the flat. Have you taken note of the address?)
What happens next? You take a lighter one
(Pollo: Who do you think I am? I am serious! A honest worker, not a wannabe small time journalist.)
you bring them out even more, and it's over
If even the foundation the colour of you skin weren't of any use
(Pollo: could you please write it again for me?)
regardless of your skin color, you purchase a corrective one
(Pingu: I knew! Via del Tasso 23, Pollo. This means yes, doesn't it?)
but don't use too much
(Pollo: I'm not the greedy asocial banker you paint me to others)
Then you fix everything up with powder. But, Bestie, extremely lightly!
(Pingu: Alessio is gonna be there too)
This is obviously only the beginnning, you'll take care of the rest later
(Pingu: That moron? C'mon, no, please!)
You could take inspiration from my tutorials
Yesterday, I filmed my 638th
(Pingu: He's Gaia's boyfriend, what were you expecting Pollo? If you care for me you'll come anyway.)
You'll be spoilt for choices
Bestie!
Bestie, are you listening to me?
Ehi! But...
Who are you texting with?
With Marco!
Marco who?
Marco my best friend, Debora!
You must have seen him, let me see...
A billion times?
Shall we leave now?
Yep, put the belt on
I don't remember him anyway
Hm, weird
(#CONNECTED)
(You won't ever believe how they replied to him!!! #conspiracy #vaccines #bastards)
It's unbelievable!
What?
Do you know about that young activist
the one who is exposing them all
Ah, is he the one about the chips under the skin?
Subcutaneous, honey, they're called "subcutaneous"
Oh, alright.
However: yes, he is
What has he said this time?
Nothing we didn't know about
I know what, you know what
and the informed ones know,
what vaccines do for real
It's not that my cousin is autistic for no reason!
It's the answers!
You should know how they replied to him!
This really is the time I get proper cross!
Calm down, honey!
Hey! Don't calm down me!
Those words make my ears bleed!
I'll spare you from those
And then I have to pay "some people"'s taxes!
You mean you pay
their wages with your taxes
No, Gaia
this is really disappointing, coming from you
It is exactly because I pay their wages, that I pay their taxes too!
If only they paid their taxes, bloody crooks
always taking on honest people
they want us as ignorant as goats, goats, goats
no offence intended, honey
No, alright
let's move on
How did they reply to him, then
It's obvious that you are dying to tell me
They told him
that he is an ignorant idiot
A brainless conspirationist
How dare some people look at the mirror in the morning?
Bunch of lobbyist-mason-bastards!
If only people got themselves informed just a little bit more...
Alas, no! And what do they do?
They vote for them, in the assumption of making their own interest
while, instead, they sling shit at society
the nation, the whole world
SHEEP!
Alessio!
Could you please quit putting innocent animals in harm's way?
Ok, honey, but they really do wave the red flag at a bull
They're all stereotypes!
Meaning?
Bulls are meek animals
It's mankind's fault for soiling their language
with mean and meaningless words
Honey, you know that I didn't intend to cause any harm!
Well, you still said it!
Have a look!
Look, honey, look at
what men are capable of
Cioè, do you know
how many scale insect does it take
to make two pounds of cochineal red dye?
Is it the first sentence of a joke?
One hundred thousands
dead bugs, Alessio!
Does it sound like a joke to you?
Is it so much fun, eh?
Now you know what you scoff together with your strawberry yoghurt?
Still with the yoghurt argument?
It's not like I forced the cow to give me her milk!
It was a yoghurt, what were you thinking?
Alright, let's drop it here, then!
(Ilaria: 15 minutes and we're home matey. I've got a bunch to tell! Marco's on his way, try not to shock him)
Ilaria is here
Ah
If Debora, stupid as she is, doesn't crash, they'll be here shortly
I told her I would pick her up on my bike
(Alessio: Chick incoming, buddy, better hurry)
(Rocco: Cooooool :D :D :D on me way)
However, Rocco is coming too
Hope it's not an issue
Your pig housemate?
Why should it?
Now, don't mix pigs with human stereotypes
Ah, however, Marco is coming too
this way we compensate
Ah, Marco!
Mr Pole-Up-His-Arse honours us with his presence
You are an asshole!
Nice sandals! German?
Franziskaner?
Christal orb, tell me the future!
Oh, oh, excuse me!
Did you know you look like Jessica Rabbit
in half?
(I'm downstairs, can you open the gate?)
(Right away)
Yes?
Ale?
Open, it's me
(I'm at your place. Don't say I don't care for our friendship)
(Is alessio talking about reptilians?)
(No, but I am about to share the lift with a maniac.
Remember I care for you)
What floor?
You?
Seventh
Me too
Coincidence
Slow, uh?
The sun came out, at last
Couldn't take any more bad weather
But you...
Yeees?
What team do you root for?
I'm not a great fan. See you later.
Come on, I can't believe you root for no team
It's been a pleasure. I have arrived.
So have I! See, what a coincidence?
Marco!
Rocco...
Have you two been introduced yet?
Eh, nice to meet you, I am Rocco, Alessio's housemate
Marco
He's Ilaria's best friend, the girl who's coming back tonight
Please, come in
So, with Ilaria, fuck buddies?
Friendzone?
Friendzone!
Debora, you parked on zebras
I have no time to waste, dearie. Let's go!
Look, they're gonna scratch this one too
Those vandals!
Debora, the suitcase! Debora! Gotta get the suitcase!
Ma...
Is he the one with the pole up his arse?
Really!
Alright
But he looks a cool guy, doesn't he?
But, hey, do we know what team he roots for?
Nah, he doesn't follow football
Don't bullshit me!
Is he gay?
No
He's Ilaria's puppy, but she...
Listen, buddy, but...
who is the cute one, Ilaria or Debora?
Both are! That's why I called you. Don't you trust me?
Come on!
Brother, the heart wants what the heart wants!
Eh, and so does the bald eagle!
So then...
I hope they'll consider me, Debora.
After all, achieving the qualification has been expensive and horribly tiring
then, after such an intensive course!
but, nowadays, keeping one's CV up to date is paramount, you know!
especially for someone, like me, who hasn't yet built a strong network
so she's forced to accept any position
(deb_mele Chat in lift #home #besties #chitchat #smile #elevator #boring #concrete)
Honey
You must see this photo of a "Daubentonia madagascariensis"
Too cute!
Are you boys socializing?
Sure, honey!
So, Marco
how is work doing?
how many poor souls have you bloodsucked today
you there at Goldman Sachs?
I'm off work today, so...
None
Oh, did you watch the derby?
Would you remind me how much you earn?
I've never told you!
Have you got anything to hide?
Let me guess...
You got your job thanks to your dad, a banker like you
No
I'm afraid it's my economy and finance
master degree's fault
Gotta pee
Your family must be very wealthy!
Yes
My dad is a bricklayer!
I knew it!
A freemason!
Matey!
Hi matey!
They're all here already
Rocco's here too
you were bound to meet him at some point anyway
After all the horrible things about him you told me about, I can't wait!
Pollo!
Naughty chick of mine!
Hi, future slave of the government!
Hi, dumbass!
One minute later and I'd have strangled him!
I'm sorry
Hello, I am Rocco, baby!
Ilaria
I have heard about you, a lot
Has anybody told you why I have got this name?
I can imagine
your mom liked the name. Let's get out.
Ciao
I am Rocco, baby!
Would you like to know why my mother gave me this name?
Have I already told you how nice you and my dad have been for bringing my stuff over here?
I was ready to sleep on the sofa, you know
20 times today alone
Don't exaggerate!
But this won't pay back for all my effort
You're a naive chick, really
you even pretended you had forgotten the address
Did I?
Yep. I must let you know
that I believe I'll never trust your words again?
Ah, right?
Right!
And here you are, the ineffable Pingu
The only one able to transform a gesture of pure altruism into a fault
I'm taking the piss, naughty chick, come on...
It's me taking the piss on you
OK
Fetch the pillow, come on!
Nooo! Oh, great, great bro!
Go Inter
No! No! No! Foul! Come on!
Pass it on! Pass the ball forward to him!
He's alone! No! Taken! I cannot bear the sight of them when they behave this way
Do you know how much money spins around football?
Oh Ale, don't fray my balls with this stuff!
I'm pretty sure
matches are all fixed
Have a look at the referee's watch
they have no shame
It's true!
Oh, holy words, brother!
Jesus Christ couldn't have said it better
Respect
Nooo! No! Again?
Noo no look, look, if you miss this... Don't miss...
Shoot! Shoot! Shoot!
Nooooo!
Do you mind?
What?
I have to send a voicemail to my sistas
and you are typing, like...
You know how!
Love of my life, ciao!
Jump immediately to watch the picture I've tagged you on
and you'll be at peace with yourselves
What I say is
did she do her own eyebrows
or did she hire a monkey to do her job?
Go watch the one I'm about to post too! Catch you later, sisters, kiss
(deb_mele Vegans, a self solving problem #vegan #starvation #bitch #fun #lovemeat  #protein #iguanodon)
You know I'm following your profile, don't you?
Giv 'a' fuck
Dunno, Marco
I sincerely hope they'll get back to me soon
I don't want to sit on my hands
It's true
I'm very tired
But also very excited
I can put myself on the line now! Make
a difference
you do understand what I am trying to say, don't you?
Yes, I do
And perhaps
perhaps you would like to be paid for it too
Says the typical materialist guy
This is a matter of passion
But passion doesn't pay the bills
Do you want to leave it in the fashion blogger's hands?
o in the dog-sitter's?
Look, Gaia doesn't deal just with dogs
Oh well
in the pet-sitter's, then
Do you realise you're the only one here
with a good head on your shoulders?
Beh... Give or take
You are really determined to rain on my parade, aren't you?
No, no, Pingu... I didn't mean it, you know that.
I know, Chick, I know.
I am not planning to get rich with a web serie
I just want to be a journalist
that which I've studied for, ok?
I know that I have to learn plenty of ropes
?????
Do you find it so absurd that I cherish the hope to get to count for something?
No
Because you're a typical careerist
Says the banker son of a bricklayer
Oh my god!
Oh my god, it's them!
Is that... About the job?
Yes, I didn't think they would call me today
What are you waiting for? Answer it!
Do you mind?
Ah, sorry!
Hello?
Yes, it's me
Ilaria Visconti
Everything alright?
Is Ilaria ok, that is?
Yes, yes, everything alright
Did she mention the job interview she had with that newspaper last week?
They have just called her
Job?
Newspaper?
Has anybody said
PARTY?
(Mangled: come on, shake your body baby, do the conga
I know you can't control yourself any longer)
I understand
They have called her so quickly
Does our dear Ilaria know someone from the Bilderberg group?
Nip it in the bud, shall we?
You nip it, so you can eat the bud!
Did you get it?
He told her "eat the bud" because she's a vegan
You, piece of shit!
It's fertiliser, honey. I do it for you!
Marco told me they called you for the job
How did it go?
I got the job
Let's celebrate right away!
No no no no no no, guys! No, no, no
They have asked me to write an article immediately
and I'm very tired
I can't
I promise you we'll do it another day
we'll celebrate properly
Though, if you could stay...
no problem with that
No, no
I'm working tomorrow, I'd better go
Sucking blood in arrears, right?
Bye guys
Bye
I think I am going
to stay here a little bit longer
Cool
What are you playing? Angry birds?
Three more deaths caused by the heat:  Killer Giasone
What are meteorologists hiding?